[crowd shouting. clamoring]
- [citizen 1] They killed the judge!
- [citizen 2] Come on!
[citizen 3] Don't
let them get away!
[clamoring continues]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[Martha] So what happened?
I haven't exactly trained for
this moment. That's what happened.
- I thought I'd be the first to go down.
- Yeah.
[chuckles] Me too.
- There's more people joining.
- We can't get past them.
We have to. It's
the only way home.
[Carla] Maybe not.
- [Carla breathes heavily]
- The porters?
You're still mixed up with them?
We just gotta make it
down two more levels.
Try to keep up.
There's no way to
argue it wasn't you.
[exhales sharply. sighs]
I don't see how.
He doesn't know the name of my
listeners but he knows the hallmarks.
He clearly traced the campaign
to impeach Meadows back to me.
[child] Mom.
Mom.
- Just a minute. honey.
- [child] There's a man in the kitchen.
Can I help you with that?
[Bernard] Can't remember the
last time I made my own coffee.
I don't speak about Mayor Jahns often.
but she always made her own coffee.
She said doing the everyday tasks
of the ordinary people of the Silo
helped her feel connected to
them when nothing else did.
[inhales sharply]
This job. you see.
requires me to have a different
perspective than anybody.
Here. let me.
That machine's finicky.
Um. I...
I'm supposed to be pretty
good with machines.
[Camille chuckles]
You used to work
with Rob. correct?
I used to work for him.
as he likes to remind me.
Does he discuss work with you?
Robert finds I'm not much
interested in that work anymore.
I have my job in IT
and I have my son.
The Pact says. "Mothers are a vessel
to deliver our children into the world.
just as the Silo is a
vessel for the people."
In our family. we
take that to heart.
Your family reads the Pact
together. I think you told me?
Every night.
Would you mind getting your
copy of the Pact for me?
Sure.
You betrayed my trust. Rob.
You made me do something
I didn't want to do.
You will no longer be
head of Judicial Security.
You will not be my shadow.
But you're too
valuable to sideline.
So you'll take Mary's
job. You'll be Judge.
Place your hand on the
Pact and repeat after me.
I. Robert Sims. do
solemnly swear...
I'm gonna go take a look.
- Calvin here?
- [Calvin] Who's asking?
Calvin. Haven't seen
you for a while.
I always stop seeing
porters after a certain age.
Knees.
You're gonna lead with an
insult. woman in your position?
You'll be lucky if any part
of you makes it back down.
[scoffs] That's why we're here.
We need a place to rest up.
and I need transport home
for me and my friends.
It'll cost you.
I may or may not have a case
of before times bourbon.
[chuckles] It's gonna
take more than old booze.
Do you have anything that
belonged to Juliette Nichols?
[grunts]
[Solo] Hi. What you doing?
Um. well. I didn't get
a firefighter helmet.
and I don't want to
go back in the water.
So I'm trying to see if
my old one could connect.
Hey. I was gonna ask.
Your generator is under a
hundred levels of water.
So. how are the lights on?
Um. IT has its own power source.
Comes from the outside.
Where from the outside?
Just up. like...
[Solo stammers]
Do you know why the
generator failed?
Um... [clicks tongue]
Yeah. some Judicial
raiders had the bright idea
of blowing up the groundwater pump
on 144 to flood out Mechanical.
But they couldn't get it fixed before
the water took out the generator.
So. the water keeps...
Right.
Do you think... [sighs]
Do you think there's a way to
stop the water from rising?
Your nearest groundwater
pump is on 30.
Underwater.
But you could run power to it.
Maybe you could
stop it from rising.
- Yeah.
- Wait. you...
You could stop it.
Me? No. no.
- I don't have time. I have to do this.
- No. I don't have time.
- I'm running out of time.
- You're not running out of time.
- You have months. Years to figure out...
- Ten months. Ten.
- I have ten months. Yeah.
- Ten months? Oh. I have days.
- Yeah. but you don't know that for sure.
- [stammers]
So why would I take that risk?
In ten months. the
water's coming into IT.
- In 13. it'll be completely under water.
- No. No. no. stop!
Look. this is what I need to do
and that is not working. okay?
- I can't connect it.
- Where are you going?
I need to go to the suit room and see
if I can find a helmet that works.
[Solo] Hey. wait!
Where are they?
They got off the stairs at
70. Multiple cameras went down
and we don't know where they are.
but I sent a team of raiders.
They're disguised as citizens
and they're stirring up
mobs from 60 down to 130.
- You put a bounty on the two leaders?
- 1.000 credits each.
Have Judicial erect a barricade at
130. in case they elude the mobs.
They won't get by my people.
Humor me. Mr. Amundsen.
I worry. That's my job.
And in the interest
of expediency.
I will overlook the use
of the phrase "my people."
Let me be very clear.
There is no manner in which
the Judicial raiders are yours.
Message just came in. We have
a location for them on 70.
[Calvin] How do
I know it's hers?
You don't.
But I do.
'Cause I'm the one who gave
it to her 20 years ago.
And I'm the one who fixed the hinge when
she used it to pry out frozen bolts.
which I told her not to do.
I'll take it. [chuckles]
Plus the two dozen refrigeration coils
you promised for your little stay.
Throw in the old booze
and. uh. we've got a deal.
- So. what's your plan?
- Grain bins.
Everyone knows the mill in 59
breaks down every other week.
No one will blink an eye at grain
on its way down to the lower mills.
- Fuck that.
- I didn't promise a comfortable ride.
I'm not asking for comfort.
It's just that we have a fourth.
Rather large. No way he'll fit.
All I got.
What about the descender rig?
- Not sure what you mean.
- [Carla] Sure you do.
[Martha] I don't.
- It's a powered winch and cable system.
- It's against the Pact.
And you acquired it in some
kind of Pact-approved manner?
We took it out of
circulation is all.
Porters have the exclusive
right to move all Silo goods.
People see something like that.
- they start getting other ideas.
- [door slams]
[Knox] We gotta go!
Raiders are coming. Let's go!
- You sent a message to Judicial.
- I was gonna help you. I promise.
But there's a price
on their heads.
One that's too high to pass
up. even for old friends.
- [Knox] McLain!
- [Carla] Son of a bitch!
[Hank] Doc Phelan says Kennedy
hasn't been to see him. [sighs]
Maybe Kennedy knows
his reputation.
Now the best get assigned to up
top and we end up with what's left.
Apart from me.
that is. [chuckles]
What is it?
I got a message from the new
head of Judicial Security.
Rick Amundsen.
What happened to Sims?
He's been sworn in as Judge.
Where's Meadows?
Dead.
Murdered.
What?
By the head of Mechanical
and his colleague.
Knox and Shirley?
[Shirley] That didn't look
like Jules's multi-tool to me.
[Martha] Hell no. it was mine.
I have no idea where hers is.
- [Carla exclaims]
- Oh. careful. careful. Okay. I got you.
- [Carla] Okay.
- [Martha] Are you okay?
Listen. we better split up
because we can't keep holding
you back. slowing you down.
The bounty's on Shirley and me.
It's even odds who's
gonna get who killed.
Let's not get maudlin about
it. Get out of here. Go.
- You're not staying.
- [Martha] What?
You may not have anticipated
this exact scenario
when you locked yourself in
that workshop 25 years ago.
But now. nobody above 125
knows who the heck you are.
That's gonna work
to your advantage.
I. however. am the
head of Supply.
- Carla. I am not going...
- Martha.
They are gonna need
you down there.
Probably now more than ever.
Go.
It's just an ordinary scrape.
You clean it with soap
and it'll heal just fine.
Let me see.
Okay. It's not too bad.
Just keep the pressure on.
I'll be right back.
Clove oil will help with the pain and
the aromatic should help you sleep.
Thanks. Smells real nice.
But I heard my shoulder pop.
Better go see the doc about that.
That's a good idea.
He's right over there.
- [bones cracking]
- [groans] That hurt.
- [grunts]
- Move it around.
Yeah.
Don't forget to
take the clove oil.
- [patient] Thanks.
- [Kathleen] Yeah.
It's an impressive technique
for someone wearing a baby.
[Kathleen] Thank you. My
mother was an herbalist.
And my father was a drunk.
who lost a lot of fights.
[chuckles] Dr. Pete Nichols.
Nice to meet you.
Kathleen Billings.
As in Sheriff Billings?
Now I know why you're out
here tending the wounded.
It's a good distraction.
I can't sit at home.
I get too anxious.
Paul was sent to Mechanical.
There was some kind of
incident down there.
- Yeah. I heard. Some kind of fire or...
- [raider 1] Dr. Nichols.
Uh-huh?
Please come with us.
Now.
What's his plan?
Have the Silo take
down the killers.
If he succeeds. it'll
be like a reset for him.
Like Juliette Nichols
never happened.
You've run missions like that.
Raiders in plainclothes.
Big bounty on the fugitives.
Mobs chase them down.
Maybe take the law
into their own hands.
A sensitive operation like
that takes experience. Rob.
Amundsen's good.
He was trained by the best.
but he isn't the best.
What if he's not up to it?
Make the most of
the job. Robert.
[knocking]
[Bernard] Yeah.
Dr. Nichols. [exhales deeply]
Thank you for coming.
If you think I know something about
those Mechanical folks. you're mistaken.
No. no. no.
No. No. it has nothing
to do with that.
I just thought that you might like
some of your daughter's things.
Under normal circumstances. these items
would be put back into circulation.
but these circumstances
are far from normal.
If these items were to be put back.
I'm afraid they would be venerated.
coveted. cause envy and dissension
and ultimately violence.
It wouldn't be the only way
that your daughter's memory
has been distorted to fit
the agendas of others.
I heard that you were tending
to people wounded in the riot
after Judge Meadows's murder.
That spirit of
service gives me hope
that you might be a bigger
part of this moment.
This movement to restore
order to the Silo
and faith in the Pact.
What if I say no?
Why would you say no?
I just want to be clear.
If I don't help
you. what happens?
There is nothing left
for me to lose. is there?
[inhales shakily] The Silo has taken
my son. my wife and now my daughter.
[inhales shakily]
I wasn't tending to the wounded
out of a sense of duty to the Silo.
I was trying to reclaim some
sense of professional integrity.
I was trying to practice medicine
without lies. without harm.
All those birth control
removals marked Code Orange.
I see those young couples.
Their faces alight with hope.
Hope that I know is unfounded.
My profession is a sham.
The Silo took that from me too.
[scoffs]
[clicks tongue] For whatever
reason. my daughter is dead.
You can't control what
she means to people.
You can't control
what she means to me.
[door closes]
[Juliette] So. Solo...
- [Solo] Yeah.
- That's not your real name. is it?
Uh. no.
- Co... Uh. Cole Myers is my name.
- Cole.
I went to an event and they
asked me. "Who are you with?"
And I said. "I'm solo."
and Russell's kid was there
and he overheard me say that
and he thought that was my
name. so the name stuck.
But... But hey.
what's in a name?
Right.
That's from your-your play.
Romeo and Juliet before they die.
Before who dies?
Romeo and Juliet.
- They don't die. No.
- Yeah. they do.
In ours. they do.
- [grunts] Fuck.
- Are you okay?
- [sighs] Yeah.
- [Solo] Hey. are you hungr...
I don't know. I just feel...
I'm tired. Just... I'm good.
Are you hungry?
- I don't know. Yeah. maybe. Maybe.
- Yeah!
- Okay. but stay...
- I'ma... Yeah. I'm gonna go get some food.
Shit. [breathes heavily]
[exhales sharply]
[grunts]
[Sharon] These are the reports
and briefings you're copied on.
If they have little flags.
they come with recommendations
from the mayor's office.
When you've reached
your decision.
- you enter...
- Sharon. I've been in Judicial
for some years now.
[Sharon] Of course. Your Honor.
We haven't been able to fabricate
your signature stamp yet.
[muffled] So. if you don't mind signing
for the time being until the stamps...
[continues talking.
indistinctly]
Judge Sims?
[Bernard] Good work.
The others?
The two we put the bounty
on are on the stairs.
I've got raiders out of uniform
just a couple levels below.
And we're whipping up the crowd.
Let me know when you have them.
Yes. sir.
[crowd clamoring]
Thank you. you can go.
Mr. Kyle.
How's your time in
the mines going?
It's only been a day.
Well. you're still alive.
That's good.
[inhales sharply] Do you know
what the life expectancy is
of someone sent to the mines?
[Lukas] No. sir.
Five years.
So when Judge Meadows cut
your sentence in half.
it was a symbolic
gesture at best.
It's unlikely you'd
survive your time there.
Do you know why?
Because it's dangerous? I...
Rockfalls. suffocation.
crushing injuries.
lost limbs.
explosions gone awry.
- [sighs]
- [Bernard] It's hard duty.
I'm going to offer you
some soft duty. Lukas.
I have a project that
requires your mind.
On the day of Judge
Meadows's murder.
she relayed to me how you were able to
take small disparate bits of information
about the lights in the night
sky and create a model that.
between you and me.
was not far off.
Is that accurate?
Well. I have something
that is also fragmented
and I need you to
reconstruct it.
You recognize it?
This is the hard drive that
Juliette Nichols showed you.
You can tell me the truth.
It won't put you in any
additional legal jeopardy.
Yes. I recognize it.
I smashed it because
it's a red-level relic
and it likely contains
dangerous information.
But now I no longer have
the luxury of ignorance.
I need you to find
out what is on it.
You can work from this office.
Do you have any questions?
Come on.
You must know that there are
at least three people out there
in the IT bullpen that can
do this better than you.
Well. Lukas. I know that
you will work harder
than anyone I can
find out there...
because. well...
you want to live
more than five years.
[door opens]
[gasps]
[sighs]
Judge. is everything okay?
You tell me.
The button isn't working.
[sighs] We have everything
handled here. Your Honor.
Your Honor?
Judge?
Call me Rob like you
have the last ten years.
I'm trying to figure this
out... [sighs] ...just like you.
I was just in my office.
My new office.
Sitting behind the desk of a woman
I worked for for the last 15 years.
Thought it might be a good idea to
see how the search for the people
who murdered her is going.
I'll make sure you get all the
relevant details on your desk
in the morning.
The suspects are
still on the stairs.
We're using the plan
you put in place.
- [crowd clamoring]
- [both panting]
- [grunts]
- Move.
You're in an awful hurry.
Hey. my. uh. husband and I were just
headed down to see some friends.
Well. that seems unwise.
Dangerous killers on the loose.
What are you all doing out?
- We're concerned citizens.
- And who are you?
Let's see some identification.
Does the Pact require citizens to
show identification to other citizens
who are concerned. or...
- It does not.
- It doesn't...
[citizen] That one's armed!
[Camille] Stop!
I said stop!
I see some of you know me.
And I know some of you too.
You know who my husband is.
What you might not know
is his new position.
Judge Sims wants these
fugitives taken into custody.
[citizens groaning. murmuring]
You want to kill them where
they stand? Well. I do too.
But justice for Judge Meadows
doesn't only belong to us.
It belongs to the Silo.
And everyone will watch when
these two go out to clean.
[citizens cheering]
[Knox. Shirley grunting]
Come with me. or your greasy asses
are getting strung up right here.
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[sighs] Okay.
[sighs]
[exhales. inhales sharply]
[grunts]
Shit.
[Camille] You'll be
safe here for a while.
You're not taking
us to Judicial?
Cameras still work on the stairs.
but they're out in this alleyway.
When they see me headed back up alone.
they'll send more raiders after you.
Maybe a lot of them. So wait
till it settles down to leave.
There's a barricade on 130.
No idea how you'll get through.
but that's not my problem.
Why are you helping us?
[knocking]
Camille.
Morning. Asa.
You're going to
work early today.
And you're staying back at
your ex-wife's tonight. on 83.
- I just finished the night shift.
- [Camille] Then your boss will just think
you're the hardest working
plumber in the Silo.
Give me your keys.
[sighs] What the fuck. Camille?
When you hear about a bounty for
the people who murdered Meadows.
you'll ignore it so that
I keep ignoring you.
[Asa scoffs]
[Camille] You understand?
Well. can I put some
pants on at least?
Don't know why you didn't
reach for those first.
[Asa scoffs]
[Hank] They been caught?
No.
It's a pretty big conflict. huh?
What?
Well. being a sheriff's deputy
while my friends are being hunted
as killers by half the Silo.
About as big as swearing
to enforce the Pact
while having a condition
expressly condemned by the Pact.
Yeah.
Do they know?
Sims knows.
As head of Judicial Security.
he made an allowance.
As judge. I...
I may have a line
on Patrick Kennedy.
Try not to eat
everything in the fridge.
I'm just a hardworking guy
whose main job is to
keep the Silo running.
- It depends what you got in there.
- Shirl.
Kidding.
How's she expect you to
get back in without a key?
Oh. [chuckles]
She doesn't.
If she wants me to have it.
she'll find a way to get it to me.
[sniffles] Word of advice.
stay as long as you need.
But if I were you. I'd be
gone before she gets back.
[stammers] I'm not helping
her out of courtesy.
Took you assholes in 'cause
I'm... I'm afraid of her.
You should be too.
[door opens]
- [door closes]
- [sighs]
[sighing]
[Knox] This guy lives
in a fucking closet.
[groans. sighs]
Do you think every department
thinks they're the ones
that keeps the Silo running?
Probably.
I have said those same words as a
way to rally everybody in Mechanical.
[Shirley] And it worked
because it's true.
Even if the rest of the
Silo believes otherwise.
[sighs]
You're a good leader. Knox.
Mechanical would have gone to shit
years ago if it wasn't for you.
I was wrong about what to do.
I wanted to ask nicely and...
Now we're gonna die for it.
We were damned from the
beginning either way.
But if we did it my way.
we'd already be dead.
[patrons chattering]
Do you think Knox and
Shirley killed Judge Meadows?
Honestly? Since Jules walked.
things have gotten out of hand.
Shirley and a mob
attacking my station.
Now Knox has teamed up with her.
They have no respect for Silo order.
Do I think they killed Meadows?
Not a fucking chance.
Hold on.
Hey. Frances. Hold up a sec.
You mind telling us where
you're going with that meal?
Uh. home?
But it's after midnight.
Your shift started at 6:00 a.m.
You telling me instead of
sleeping. you're gonna stay up
and eat the same food you've been
slinging for the last 18 hours?
Unless they passed a law against that.
Hank. yeah. that's what I'm doing.
[Paul] We know your
history. Frances.
Doris Kennedy was your aunt and you
sold some of the pills she stole.
You got some proof about that? 'Cause
you sure as fuck didn't five years ago.
Whoa. whoa. Franny. We
ain't here about that.
We're here because we
figure your Uncle Patrick
isn't gonna live much
longer on hot meals alone.
So why don't you
let us deliver that?
[Sims groans]
How was your first
day. Judge Sims?
I signed where directed.
I went to the Watcher's room.
Tried to get some
intel on the search.
Amundsen wouldn't let me in.
He did tell me three of the
suspects were still at large.
Well. if you were in charge.
they'd have been in
custody hours ago.
[crowd shouting. clamoring]
[Sandy] Excuse me. please.
I live in 132.
Not tonight you don't.
I work for the sheriff's department.
Whatever this is. we weren't informed.
[raider] This doesn't concern
the sheriff's department.
Look. if Judicial thinks they can
keep citizens from their homes...
Turn around and go
back the way you came.
[scoffs] Are you serious?
You have no right to interfere
with someone who is a member
of the sheriff's department.
- I need to get...
- [shouting. clamoring continues]
The second we hit the
stairs. they'll see us.
And as soon as we close
this door. we're locked out.
We got to go home sometime.
I say we hit the stairs
and run like hell.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Okay.
But not down.
- Up.
- What?
Trust me.
[inhales deeply. groans]
[Amundsen] They were caught in a mob.
A former raider stashed them on 73.
So we checked every residence.
Got nothing so far.
- but I've locked down the trash chute.
- [Bernard] Hold on.
Why did an ex-raider
stash them on 73?
She was concerned they
might be strung up.
[stammers] Who was she?
Camille Sims.
Find those fucking Mechanicals.
- How far are we going up? [grunts]
- [Shirley] Just keep up.
[debris clatters]
[Juliette grunts]
[sighs]
[sighing]
[Lukas] I was able to
salvage very little.
I found some fragments that
overlap with files in our database.
Uh. this is our Silo map.
and I've been using this file to
fill in some of the missing data
from one of the fragments.
which is also a map.
And now it differs from our
Silo map in a few places.
There are lines that are coming
from outside the Silo walls.
There's something on the IT
level and something on Judicial.
Any idea what they are?
No. Uh. there's something else.
- There. at the very bottom of the Silo...
- [Bernard] What is it?
- [Lukas] A tunnel.
- Where does it go?
I have no idea.
[Bernard] Well. keep working.
You've earned another 24 hours
outside of the mine. Mr. Kyle.
Sir. there was a... a
folder also that I found.
Uh. I was able to retrieve
it uncorrupted. and...
and look. most of the files in it
were just these department memos.
but one of them was different.
Um. it was a scan of a handwritten
letter someone wrote his wife.
Who?
Salvador Quinn.
What did it say?
Well. it's a love letter. but
then it gets kind of weird.
- It sort of... It goes into this. uh...
- It goes into code.
Yeah. that's exactly right.
[Hank] Watch where you step.
Hey.
[Paul sighs]
[Paul] Patrick Kennedy.
Don't move.
[Patrick] That's
good advice. [sighs]
It really doesn't
feel great when I do.
If you come any closer. I'm
gonna throw myself in this hole.
[Paul] We're staying put. but
your wounds need treatment.
[Patrick] Yeah. it's
funny. you know.
with the guns. it looks like you're
gonna give me some fresh ones.
[Hank] You're a fugitive. seen
fire-bombing my deputy station.
You understand why we
might be a little cautious.
[Paul] We can help you.
[breathing heavily]
I don't trust you.
That's why I'm down
here in the dark.
bleeding in a fucking hole!
There's a full med kit
- in the generator control room.
- Go. go.
Mmm.
[breathing heavily] That
what you're waiting for?
Now that we're all
alone. you shoot me
and hope that Deputy Longhair didn't
count the holes in me before he left?
We don't shoot people who
don't pose an immediate threat.
I pose an immediate threat.
The things I know. you'd
be better to leave.
I can't do that.
I took an oath. Part of that
is rendering available aid.
[shouting] Rendering
available aid?
Don't you see that
it's all a lie?
Everything they told us.
The Pact.
It's just to keep us in line.
And we will never ever
find out the truth.
Sims would shoot each one of us
before he'd let that shit happen.
You know Mr. Sims?
[Patrick] Yeah. I know him.
I helped Nichols out.
I was gagged and bagged.
Why do you think I'm down here?
Tell me.
[wincing. breathing
heavily] Okay.
Okay. Sure. I'll tell you.
Just give me your gun.
That's right. You can't
'cause you don't trust me.
Look. if you're gonna shoot me. all I
ask. just put it right here. all right?
Please. [breathing shakily]
[Paul] I found this
in Juliette Nichols's apartment.
In a book.
I destroyed the rest.
I couldn't tell you
why I saved that.
You tell anyone I have
that. I'm finished.
Get me a doctor. Not a
deputy with a Band-Aid.
And I'll tell you
everything you want to know.
No. I'll tell you everything you
sure as fuck don't want to know.
[groans]
New deal.
[Shirley] How long is the cable?
Guess you'll find out.
[Calvin grunts]
This? It's not Juliette's.
But fuck you if I'm gonna
let you sell it as hers.
[grunts]
[battalion leader]
Barnes. pick it up.
Come on.
- [Amundsen] You have an update?
- Not yet.
[Amundsen] Look for any groups
of two moving down the stairs.
[Diego] Copy.
Level 92. Two
porters headed down.
I'm not far behind. Get
a message to the mayor.
Copy.
[Solo] I've got dinner.
[footsteps approaching]
What ya doing?
Um. I was trying to track down a helmet
that was stolen from the suit room.
So I went to an employee's
apartment. trying to find it.
Trina Samuel's.
Yeah. She was Solo's girlfriend.
Yeah. I haven't thought
about her in a long time.
Actually. I... I... I don't
like thinking about her.
Do you want chicken or beef?
Why are you lying to me?
[stammers] I don't know
what you're saying.
Solo. Trina. That's her.
That's not you. is it?
No. 'Cause this... Look
at this. I found this.
Cole Myers. the IT shadow.
- That's the actual... [gasps]
- I am the IT shadow!
You don't know what
you're talking about!
Don't say those words
to me! Don't you ever!
- I am Solo!
- [Juliette whimpers]
[shouting] I am the IT
shadow. do you hear me?
- Okay.
- I am Solo! I am the IT shadow!
[Juliette whispers] You're Solo.
You're Solo.
I'm sorry.
[breathes shakily]
[breathes shakily. winces]
[groaning]
You look terrible. You should
really have something to eat.
[Juliette breathing shakily]
[whispers] I'm not hungry. Um...
[normal] I. uh...
I don't feel well.
I need to just. um...
I'm gonna lie down.
I'm just gonna...
This far enough down?
[Shirley] I think so.
Now. will it hold your ass?
That I don't know.
[Knox grunts]
[Amundsen] Mechanical!
Stop!
- [Shirley] Fuck.
- Shit.
- [Shirley] Come on.
- [Amundsen exclaims. grunts]
There's no brake. is there?
There's the cable. and
there's the end of the cable.
[Shirley breathes heavily]
At least we'll die
in the Down Deep.
[breathes heavily]
[both screaming]
[cable whining]
[both groaning. grunting]
[Down-Deeper] Give me your hand!
[both grunting. groaning]
- [gunshot]
- [cable snaps. whirs]
[crowd clamoring]
[Knox grunting. screams]
[grunting]
[panting]
[grunts]
- [Down Deeper 2] Watch out.
- [clamoring]
- Fuck!
- [Knox panting]
- [Up-Topper 1] There they are!
- Get them!
[crowd clamoring]
[Down-Deeper 3] Watch out!
[clamoring]
- [Bernard] Fuck!
- [Amundsen] They got through. sir.
I noticed.
Keep this channel clear.
Sheriff Billings. do you copy?
[grunts]
Sheriff Billings.
[Paul] Yes. Mr. Mayor?
Sheriff. I regret to inform you
that the fugitives from Mechanical
just became your problem.
I know that as a loyal
servant of the Silo.
I can count on you
to bring them in.
Of course. Mr. Mayor.
You can always count on me to
faithfully serve the Silo and the Pact.
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
Come on. [inhales
sharply. grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[sighs. groans]
[groans]
[grunts. breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[groans. pants]
[groaning]
[groans. grunts]
[panting]
[winces. panting]
[groans]
[sighs. breathing heavily]
[gasps. panting]
[groaning]
[groans]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today